Assalam walaikum everyone welcome to my
YouTube channel humara with life pe if you are new
then subscribe to my channel like
comment share don't forget to press the bell
icon today's beautiful day has started with the
prayer that wherever you are you all remain happy, with this we continue our today's vlog, I have
just woken up from sleep, so my
tea is nice, it is raining outside today, I have
heard how is the weather
outside, it
is good, the sunshine has come out
and here I had kept some clothes after washing them.
I think I should take a look at them.   Let me
separate them a little.  These do not dry quickly.
Fahdara [nasal sound]
tear the dress, Pakhada rah
Pakhada rah tear the
dress, bring the paper and
bring it
[nasal sound]
so guys, we are going now, we have to buy clothes for working.
How is it
one day, buy clothes of your choice, comments came,
children bought clothes, they brought their choice,
Eid
brought their choice,
people praised, you buy clothes,
you children brought them, you did not bring them, you
only buy your clothes, you choose children,
drink water, it is very hot
today, there is no rush in the market, I am feeling
hot, so there is
hummus, there was hummus earlier also, there is
breeze, there is
no breeze till the square, so there is no breeze, so guys
we have come here and we have got this
kind of pair from them, look outside, it is not
very long.  He is short in height,
right?
Yes, that's right.   That's
right, that's right.  Made a bag and also waved a
little.
How accurate?
How many pairs should I buy?
Four.   Not the
same, not
different.   Not only this,
but also change the color of this shirt.  Isn't it
?  I'm liking it.
This is on the whole.
It matches perfectly with the paint.  He is saying, turn it towards
me.
They are saying that this is the entire pair, so if the shirt is
changed then the pair will get spoiled.   Okay, that's
fine.  Now how would that one look like that
brown year.
Show this line also in this line.   I am
showing it.  How will this pear of ours look in this line
?
This also looks good, right?
This one is for Fahad, right?
Yes.   Is the
board not long?
No, it will not be long.   It
is a little thick.   Take
this out for yes.
How much is healthy?  It's just like me.
You are smart.   There is
no one to take care of you.  She is my sister.
[laughs]
You will come to your place easily.   Please come and
kill me also.  Yours and mine,
check it,
keep it, I don't have a
lot of time, I am not able to get it changed,
friend,
this one is pending, I will wear it later and that one,
now I have shown some more things,
show something good to the baraat, sorry,
show something good for the wedding,
what kind of pair should we have for the wedding, we will
see that, let me
show you the baggy t-shirt,
how is
this t-shirt, let's see, you are
right, numbered, baggy, yes, the t-shirt should be
open, okay,
okay, a baggy t
-shirt should be worn with a baggy t-shirt,
okay, it will look good, it will look
good,
you should know about matching, you should know about matching, yes,
you should know about your matching,
someone should match it, come on,
you decide, match the shirt, give me these
colors, friend, these
two colors,
I will show you the shirt, it is a shirting,
check how the fabric is, it is
stretchy, see this and this fabric is
stretchy for evergreen,
okay, right now I will show you whatever goes with these,
okay, I have just
come from the shop, I said, take it for Eid
People had praised it, it is
not open, they will dance in it,
otherwise it is baggy, baggy is okay,
this is a thick fabric,
you have shown it to be light, this is thick, the
fabric in this is also thick brother, you will feel the heat of the house,
brother, get a black shirt to match the blue shirt, it is a
pale pink
fabric, it is jersey, it is hot, it will feel hot, the
heat is very light, light
fabric, the fabric should be light, they should not feel hot, hello, do this in sky blue with dark blue, yes that, yes, yes, you will check with the skirt, light, this light skirt is okay, light, right, our weight is right, yes, okay, the print is
so cute, is
n't it, my print is very simple, friend,
take a full sleeve, what are you buying,
two,
yes, take one, one, sleeves, one, one,
full sleeve shirt, it is
full sleeve, by the way, no sleeves, no sleeves, it looks like a dark
colour, so
brother, it is very
hot, my t-shirt,
come here, my
chin,
you should do half, friend, then if you go to me,
then this is fine,
yes, these are also useful,
see, yes, sleeves  I don't carry big ones these days,
look at this one on the side,
look how cute this one is,
yes on the side,
these two are
okay, this tree,
yes, let's stick
with this,
by 14th August the worms came out, the hot worms did
not come out, they did not come out, the print is lying
here, it is full of
charm,
check this,
yes, this is good
brother, I know brother liked that card, do
n't do it like this,
yours is right now,
and just
China, I
mean,
1 million,
see, people are standing there,
making a vogue bun, the
camera is not right, the
hand was also standing, make mistakes, all of them are
looking so cute, this one is
not live, what will you
think, will
eat something, right,
go to this side, she is
in jeans,
we sat there first, come forward, we should do
visiting, they are buying such cheap clothes,
Spice Spice,
if I give you the register, then register five, then 10, 10,
27, bring the account, good bag,
this is also for the children,
good, right, come here, this is
also for the children,
what have you
ordered, I said, come, I will show you
because  In this I made a vlog outside,
you have to give review in it.  Ok.
Loss.
So guys, ours now.
So guys, now we have come and sat
in the car.  There is a huge rush in the markets on 14th August.   There is a
storm brewing inside us.
So right now we are going, I am
not sitting here watching the video, friend, I have my iPhone's
video,
first let's go to your channel, so guys, I have
just bought father's clothes, now
I have to buy some makeup,
so my friend is coming, I am going with her,
Mahanoor's
and Rush, look at all of them,
so guys,
Marina is looking very strange.  I myself am
very nice, our friend has come.  We are going to get
makeup.  Let's see
what we get.  I told him I want to get some
good things for him.  She said it was good, guys, I didn't
know about makeup earlier,
I don't do so much makeup.  I my
friend know that first I am loaded, then what is
Noor, you have to get me that
spray as well, the makeup, I don't mean the
control makeup,
yes, get that as well, get that as well,
concealer, I don't know what kind of
makeup it is, primer, primer,
primer, right, and
ten other makeups, I have to get them first, I have to do the makeup, I will do it
once, go home, then teach me also, okay, okay guys,
rush, big guys, I am looking good, I have to get a
filter, make a filter, friend, it is
daylight, then it is
very small,
bye, I will get ready and
meet you, yes,
okay, done, okay, Tanu is
not visible, I have come, well done, oh yes yes, take
out the bag, brother, I had to
keep the bag here, oh I have brought it, friend, come
forward,
this lady has to go to the washroom and she is going to the washroom, this
lady has to go to the washroom and this
Marina has to
go here, she has to
go here,
not here,
she is
made upside down.  Do you want to go here,
Uncle
Bhai, to stay there [laughs]?
Yes, I was joking with you.  Go that way.
She is stuck.
Both got stuck.  I [laughs]
we're stuck here, man.
Catch that bump.  First I am from the washroom.
I feel like a homebody.   He has
come from home.  Friend, please give
me a little bit of a slap in the face.
So it doesn't break.  He raises the stake but it does
n't break.   take
care of it.   Not just
two.   Get
my dupatta checked
here, the dupatta
is wet, keep it like this with your mobile,
this
dupatta, look,
both the dupattas should be like this, I have come, I am
so busy, I know,
I also have to go to the washroom on foot, now catch this, she is not
going yet, she is
saying take the camera also, I have to go and get it, it is a
dupatta, it is a pair, if you wish, then it is
my Maya pair, then don't object to the pair, the dupatta is a dupatta, I
agree, but
not a pair, then I have to have someone, the dupatta is a
zero dupatta, guys, it is tight, then
I have to take my purse also, my mobile also,
then like this I am not
tied, so
clean it and take it away, oh, there are marks on my bag, come on, my
dupatta [laughs]
guys, look, this girl is very nice of mine,
I can take only that person with me, who
knows me, who I trust,
I can even hand over my purse to him, I do
n't get any tension, this is my man, who is trustworthy,
people were saying that go with that girl,
oh clever, clever  No, keep the rate root, it is of big gold, that
too of big gold, he is
clever but he is honest, he should be clever, he should be
honest too,
this has to be done, just come on, let's
take the menu, but friend, friend, I do
n't know who has it, let's
freshen up, I have had cold water to wash my face, I am feeling comfortable, we will arrange for a
comfortable parking, we will arrange a
rate root, come let's go, I have come to buy my
makeup,
I have brought my sister's makeup,
whose mall is it called,
Hyperstar,
yes, we have come
here, guys,
I can't hear your voice, please don't use words, the
shampoo is not good, I am
saying that my head is sweating, no, no,
keep an eye on this, this one, I don't know whether it will
suit me or not, should I buy it, anyway,
which one do I use?  Just Mac, then
Mac
Mac is also good, there are no grains in it,
yes
where is Mac,
oh look, look, there is rice one in it,
yes take this,
I will also take one rice one in the rice one,
ours is also finished,
this one is also there brother, ours is just for use, take it in
rice, more
rice, it is better in rice, take it in rice,
oh someone forgot his glasses, oh look,
I said maybe someone forgot, yes yes
these are
lying there, underarm is
needed, it is on top,
not underarm,
this one of mine has become 500, how much do you
buy it for, yours is for ₹200
promotional, there is a
sale of ₹310.  One for me is Lalla
clothes Lalla.  Some lovely fragrance
purple, look at it,
it is so much fun, but this is not
jam, look at it, the
promotion ones
too, okay brother, look at it, you have to see the
perfume, okay,
this is also the same, buy the
same thing because one has to
go towards ours,
you also have to keep this, keep it,
no, go buy something,
come on, now
tell me what do you want to buy next, now guys, I have given you the kudi das, it becomes hot
later, friend, it becomes hot after
12 hours, after six hours, it becomes hot,
shampoo is done, face wash is done,
what is this, I have
also done the test
carefully,
guys, she is saying that we will get the makeup
checked here and then we will decide which
skin it will suit, she is saying that
it is good for open pores,
after that she is
saying base color to base with color tone,
as I told you, after
checking they are telling
what a good thing is, rather, they have
given it a special one.   I am
not able to see your face, right?
Not the face you are making.  And the second
thing is possible, if possible then
you can guide us a little regarding our flat which seems to be off.  Please
guide me wearing a mask as to
which things are pay off.  So
you can keep roaming around if you want.  We'll bring you a
little more in videos and so on.
So show me what gift you have sent for Amara.
What is this?  This is DermaShine's fish gift.
You should try this,
good good good and after that there
is this face wash from Dermashine.   fixed bugs.
This is Sketchy.  Guys, look at this cute little sketch,
we have
got gifts from this company.
Thank you very much.  This is also good.  You can apply this while doing makeup.   It
is exactly like that.
Thank you very much.  So tell me, do you have any other
payoffs?  Yes, yes,
we have discounts on many things
and on the anniversary, especially tomorrow,
14th August,
we are giving flat 47% off on Rivaaz HD.
Wow,
show me what's in it?  Yes, let me
show you this one,
okay, there will be a
flat 47% off on this and
you can give it away for 14th August,
47% is
not available even today, but you can
come tomorrow, imagine, imagine, give me
time for two days,
today is 14th August,
give me an off today because I have to purchase something, there is a
special off
tomorrow, give me
time today, otherwise I will have to come tomorrow, this is
30% off right now, but tomorrow,
Insha Allah, there is a 47% off of
47,
yes no no, give me the menu
today, boss, take it, come and give me today,
how good, I
mean, if any customer comes, you
can get him a free facial, you
can get his pre-facial done, yes, you will do a
pre-facial, no, not like this,
you can get it done, get my
facial done, you
can get makeup done, you can get a free facial from us,
and get
my derma done,
okay, who will make my video,
I will make it, take it,
see how beautiful his makeup is, no, no, no,
give me the menu off, and also see,
this is my gift  Menu [ __ ] is also a gift
if you check what all food is there.
Yes, check it there.
Come take
care of those things, I am here.
Yes,
25% off is available on our cute company
and this is a very
good perfume.
This
is cute skin care and let it guide you.
So my skin is bad.  Do the menu.   These are
skin care products, ma'am.
Like it has face washes in it.
Dry oily skin is for all skin types.
Apart from this, we have serums
, sunscreen, light and day cream.
Apart from this, its shampoos are quite good.
Its dry shampoo is very good.
My hair is dry and oily.  That is
because those whose scalp remains very oily.  It
controls your oil.  Leaves
your hair fresh.
Often dry shampoos
come in spray form.  Shampoos that come in spray form do
not make your hair smooth and silky, but instead make it more
stiff.  So this dry shampoo is
in powder form.  And this is your powder,
it is in powder form.  It
is in powder form like this.  When you taste it a little on its scrap.
Then you will brush with that brush for
some time.  Let it remain for 5 minutes.
Then after that, if you brush your hair,
your hair will become completely fresh.
You don't even need to wash the job right now.
Then there is no need to wash it.
Wow, so we need a new market.   It
is like that.   That means you
just have to bring the powder.  If we have to take it or have to
go somewhere, then apply powder to clear your oily scalp.
After that you may be
travelling.  You may have gone out of town
or gone somewhere for a trip.
You can't take a bath.
I have a discount of 1875 from this, will you give me
this after discount, look at
my end, listen guys, I have a
sister's wedding, I have given you a little more
discount, I will
show you buy one get one, I will
not give you my sorry, I will not salute you,
boss, buy one get one, I will
show you get it checked,
okay buy one get one, that is, one
day
buy two get one, buy one get one, now see this is a
natural face wash, sorry, it is a serum,
this is a hair serum,
you will buy two because it is for
your skin, it is for your
skin, it is a good
skin brightening serum, you buy two,
with that you get one free,
how much is this,
these two are for 1724, then you get 115, that is, there is a
promotion going on,
these are two, that is, I have written the price of one,
one free with two, this is the
price of one, this one, okay guys, there is a
big promotion going on, today you
came at the right time, but 14th August did not come, there was a
big 14th August promotion with me, boss, boss,
you see, this is free, you buy a paste worth 285
You are buying a brush
but the paste is of Madi Cam,
Madi Cam, it was for
285,
yes, for 285 you are getting a brush as well,
give it to me,
this is good, right? Yes,
I have bought this thing in gel form,
you see, I am buying these two face washes
and the sunscreen which is worth Rs 900,
you are getting it for free.
Well, this sunscreen is free, along with this you will get
two face washes for Rs 1290 and the
sunscreen is also absolutely free for you.
And this is a very good brand, apart from this,
if you buy this lotion then this removing
cream is free for you.
Okay okay okay guys, see, whatever
promotion they brought from 14th August has come, it will
continue even after that.   It
will continue even after 14th August.  Right now
our anniversary is going on for the whole month.   The
whole month is going on.   Is it a
full month
anniversary?
Anniversary store our like
how many years has our store been built so this is
good good its anniversary.  Well
guys, this store's anniversary is going on and
they have brought a promotion and
that is whitening.  Bala folder hai wo den
idhar ekni hai.  It will cover your acne.
Ok?  One of the new ones is cinamide.  This is
for all skin types and reduces the
barriers of your skin like
dark spots, blemishes etc.
Ok,
good.  Now the third one is
how much pigmentation will it give you, then
you know that if one is for 115 then you will get
three for 2200 and if you
listen to my advice and buy three for its actual price then you do
not have to pay 1100 but I have told you that after
cutting the 1400 part we are giving it for 1100,
one discount is that if you buy two then
you are getting one for free.   That
means the total price is Rs 2200.
Just let it be
then.
Wow, your look has changed.
They did such lovely makeup on me, man.
So take this thing from them.  Show off your eye makeup.   It hasn't happened yet.
Ok.   The
rest of its makeup is very good.
No, I have closed it.  Was far away.
Look at this I am closing it.  Amara, you will have to do
such makeup.  But they did
not do it on your neck,
you will have to do it yourself, the
water should be at
one place, do it quickly, it has to be at
one place, guys, look at my face
first, I started cutting the fish, Durma, I said, come on,
I did not get time, I
said, let's cut it, Durma,
rice, the
chola wala,
that is the chola wala, it is fishy,
not the chola wala, we have to do the
chola wala, there is nothing in it, we will do it with fighting, this is better, open the car tomorrow, maximum how much time will it take, give profit in the rate, discount, the discount of 14th August has started, makeup controller, wow, makeup controller, it looks good, I will take this, pink pink, you have done too much,
it has been done too much, pink pink,
ok,
madam sat here,
madam kept waiting, she wanted to get it done today itself, she is
unconscious,
come and have fun, then
how good, friend, I have done the makeup, I
mean, they got me ready, the brother
called us for biryani, he is saying let's taste it, come,
open the Zee news, you are here, gee,
we are from the dirt people, we have biryani,
one minute,
we have prepared biryani  Is.  We get the test done.
Yes, yes, get it done.  Give me another biryani.
Just keep one like this.  Open it here.   To
unite.  First you test it and then view it.
This is my video again.  Come on, I
also have
their biryani.
You have added a little too much masala, you have
checked so much biryani,
now you will tell me it is
good,
yes it is good, no it tastes good
with the boti, I am
again saying put water here,
I think the taste of one spice in it is
not good, the boti
is good, it is good, it is fun, it is made well, guys
you all should also come and
eat biryani from them,
this is their new one, where should it come in
board star, we will make you
taste the biryani, it is prepared with Dard masala,
our promotion is on,
you will get this 140 pack of Dard masala for ₹95,
you will get Amla.  Thank you so much.
Good.
Let's
see the masala.
This is biryani masala pulao.
This is their Shami kebab.   I have served
biryani.  Biryani masala itself
is out of stock.
O egg was sold biryani masala.
Went out of stock.  Our biryani is
turning out very well.  Guys with us,
their biryani is really very good.  You
also come and say bye.
Their stock is out now.  I was doing promotion, friend.   It's
fun to
keep it in it or eat it.   For this, give it to me,
it is right
here, not on the back side,
yes, rather sister is sister, sister [laughs], sister is sister, sister, give me sister, she gets
angry with her sister also,
my sister-in-law,
I called her friend, you are my sister, I
love you, come on,
who is right,
their [laughs] set is there, their set is equal, it is
equal, if I want to
see something else, I will see that, it seems like
12 13, no no, take it, it's okay.
So guys, we're sitting here.  She is
looking so cute here, there is some good makeup and other things, I will get them for
her.  No highlighter
etc.,
no concealer, first of all.  Okay, that
means you should take the cream, the
primer,
yes, highlighter, which gives your face
color, face
powder, face concealer,
concealer,
yy, I mean, I am very tired, I have sat down, I should take
face powder, give it to you, let's
leave it, what are
you guys doing,
they did
not get their vandi checked, brother,
how is she,
I have brought fish biryani
also [laughs], I
found a girl, I have brought
biryani for you, you came and
said, I have brought biryani for you, I
said, take it, these are my hands,
look how small your hands are [laughs],
so guys, right now she is keeping the stuff in the trunk, keep it, keep it, keep it, come on, come on,
dear children, come on, come on, there is
big stuff ahead too, so guys,
we came home, okay, and after coming back
we were so tired, so tired that as soon as we
came, all three of us fell asleep, you know, all
three of us fell asleep, and
Marina did such a shameless kind of prank with me, I don't know
what should I tell her, what did she do,
this time I am so angry at her that what should
I tell you,
just do it.
She had become serious guys, she starts
doing all kinds of mischief
without informing, you should just play a prank without informing,
son, I can't agree to the next prank, she must be
serious too,
I didn't agree, guys guys,
I pranked
her without informing her and she became so serious that
she beat her face, I got some
peace, I didn't beat her after getting my face beaten,
why don't
you call me, friend, please I
know are you serious, I am not in a
good mood, the reason is your tap road, so
yes, after that she is not calling me,
I am not calling, she is
not behaving like this, what all did you
try to see, she
checked the accident prank, you try.
Accident prank
accident prank he did to me.
I asked her what do you mean she is
looking for an excuse?  I want to see your love, I want to
see your love, I want to see you in a dirty way, people have ruined your mind, I have taken you, I have married you, I am not your wife, I am not your wife, I am not
your wife, I want to see you in a dirty way ...
Mahnoor said to me, I said I had an
accident and there was a
commotion from above about 14th August, he thought it had
really happened,
I said go and bring a car that can drive, go and load it with
heat, then brother, he said I had an
accident, it's all over brother, you didn't even
put me in one, what did you
say, Baji, no, yes, Baji, brother, I am
very serious, Hari Sahab just turned around and said,
I pranked him, I came in the car, I hit it and made a
sound, it was a surprise, I do
n't know if she is dead, then after hitting it
I made a sound, oh yes yes, but I went,
I was losing hope, guys, where did I go,
no, I went [laughs] then
I would have called an ambulance, I would have called one five to three, I would have said that
I would not have cut the call [laughs] it was a
very heavy prank within two minutes, guys, I played a very heavy
prank on her, but that is her
condition  She is looking so bad,
I did not put that in Vogue, such a scattered face, this
red face, oh I am also very young, Mahnoor, unsi
chhnaada Mahnoor, I am not chhna,
I am not thinking that I will do it tomorrow, no,
nothing, I will not
prank you, please sorry to you,
my clear refusal, prank to either
guy, I will not do horror pranks,
random things,
I am not a human being, if someone comes, he will be serious,
okay, he is not my mind, I am not my
heart, I am not my serious also, guys,
I am very scared, but poor girl,
I did not call you, okay, guys, Allah is
angry, nothing, I will agree, come and
see the scene, I will love you,
I will not agree,
you will sit and watch it
[laughs] guys, I am not a serious person, I am not a serious person, I am not
ashamed at all,
I am checking according to you,
no, I
mean, then my belief is not true, Allah has not benefited me, no, it is
right, then Allah has not benefited me, no, it is not
true, then Allah has not benefited me, I am
not
a human being  I can't believe it, it was a lot of
fun,
but I am also regretting this mistake that
I got scared, I didn't come on my own,
why are you,
because you are not just pranking me,
I am making a vlog thinking it to be serious, friend, I did not get the
police registered in your vlog, he said
come quickly
[laughs] it's a
joke, come on, no,
Allah Hafiz, guys, embarrass me, okay, I
pranked you, I am
not mine, today don't prank me, I will be
rude, I will
prank you tomorrow, I will say no,
you also don't do it, you will also be
pranked, my condition is
very bad, friend,
why should you take revenge, I will take revenge, I did
not hit you, please you know
how I will go away, I will come quickly, I will shout, I will make you suffer, I will get naked, I will
break my gestures,
please don't do it like this, please I will hit you with my
fists, you should see at least
son, what should I do, don't go away
Guys wait and watch
guys no, I will not refuse him, yes Allah
what will I do, please don't play such a prank on me,
why are you,
I will die, come on,
why are you, it is a
long journey, thinking how will I reach there,
I am not in hours brother, no, no, I will faint, it is very
difficult for me, I know, the
time you met me, the whole journey got ruined, I got beaten up, I curse you, I am
angry with you,
you have done such a low thing, by the way those two also got
beaten up, I also got beaten up, the whole
neighborhood gathered in a car,
a car came, a crowd gathered,
everyone gathered, where did
I get in, it seems this moon has got into my marriage.